I'm humbled and honored in this
introduction to continue
continue. I plan to establish a
nonprofit mobile app clinic with private
foundations and development
funds and uh and I thank you again very
much for your
[Applause]
I thank all those who nominated me and
the selection committee for this
recognition. Six decades
ago, we were a
minuscule and unknown
community. We were the of the world.
In one neighborhood, I overheard someone
saying he's a
mix. In another neighborhood, they asked
me that if I was a Puerto
Rican, we'll take
you. In another neighborhood, they asked
me if I was a
city. Since then, the community has
grown
enormously. We are in every corner.
suburb and vicinity of
Cleveland. When someone meets us
now, he says, "You are so smart, you
must be Indian."
[Applause]
On a visit to
India to see my
parents, I met my wife
Sosh and married her 55 years ago.
When my immigration papers came, I asked
her to accompany me to
Cleveland. She said where it
is. I showed her a postcard
saying Cleveland is the best location in
the
nation. She was not
impressed. Then I
said Falls is only a day drive
from
Cubra. She had seen
Mara
movie. She said how exciting. I
hope she was the first female of the Mad
My son
said he was going to the public
elementary
[Music]
school.
Okay. One day after school, he asked
me where were his
feathers. He he went on to become a
neurologist. His wife El is also a
neurologist. They have two sons Raj and
Ash. My daughter
Sun My son was going to the Bwood
Elementary
School. The school asked
them to sell light bulbs for Israeli
bonds. When she went house to
house, they said, "A little Indian girl
selling bulbs for Israeli bonds, you
should buy from
her." She sold the most
bulbs and went on to get her MBA from
Cleveland
State. Her husband George is an auto
surgeon.
They have a son Shan and daughter
Saba. My life began in Cleveland due to
one
individual. Robert M was the executive
director of Neighborhood Center
Association whom I met in Chicago.
Bob brought me to Hungarian and Italian
neighborhoods of Bakai Woodland as a
community
organizer. He became my
mentor, guide and a
friend. Cleveland leaders have always
faced tough challenges.
It is due to your leadership that has
become a major strength on the
lake and Delhi and then you have wor the
fabric of all
communities. I sell it to
you ladies and gentlemen. Thank you very
much for your presence here this
evening.
[Applause]